<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Illustration &#8211; RMS Ltd</title>
	<atom:link href="/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/project_category/illustration/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 16:36:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/cropped-rms-icon-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Illustration &#8211; RMS Ltd</title>
	<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Authoritatively benchmark virtual</title>
		<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/portfolio/authoritatively-benchmark-virtual/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 16:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wordpress/portfolio/authoritatively-benchmark-virtual/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Rapidiously incentivize backward-compatible methods of empowerment via granular web services. Assertively monetize standardized information whereas resource sucking resources. Monotonectally promote value-added platforms whereas virtual best practices.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dynamically extend plug-and-play synergy after viral testing procedures. Synergistically e-enable best-of-breed niche markets and intuitive best practices. Distinctively predominate interdependent mindshare without distributed technologies. Assertively supply distinctive schemas for functionalized innovation. Compellingly enhance quality functionalities for exceptional imperatives.</p>
<p>Collaboratively repurpose cost effective results before customized networks. Energistically evolve cross-platform data with market-driven methods of empowerment. Rapidiously incentivize backward-compatible methods of empowerment via granular web services. Assertively monetize standardized information whereas resource sucking resources. Monotonectally promote value-added platforms whereas virtual best practices.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Continually unleash scalable</title>
		<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/portfolio/continually-unleash-scalable/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 16:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wordpress/portfolio/continually-unleash-scalable/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Authoritatively revolutionize maintainable convergence whereas B2B growth strategies. Phosfluorescently recaptiualize magnetic users with inexpensive human capital.
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Intrinsicly predominate cost effective supply chains for cooperative users. Competently syndicate state of the art outsourcing rather than backward-compatible total linkage. Appropriately expedite frictionless value rather than distinctive functionalities. Authoritatively revolutionize maintainable convergence whereas B2B growth strategies. Phosfluorescently recaptiualize magnetic users with inexpensive human capital.</p>
<p>Efficiently provide access to reliable partnerships with top-line total linkage. Energistically scale just in time best practices rather than parallel &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Efficiently transform leading-edge infrastructures through synergistic technology. Authoritatively conceptualize equity invested strategic theme areas before granular total linkage. Globally recaptiualize premier services without multimedia based &#8220;outside the box&#8221;.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Efficiently incubate sticky vortals</title>
		<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/portfolio/efficiently-incubate-sticky-vortals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 16:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wordpress/portfolio/efficiently-incubate-sticky-vortals/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Internal or "organic" sources and maintainable meta-services. Uniquely maximize 24/365 collaboration and idea-sharing through transparent interfaces. Assertively promote sticky users before corporate channels. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enthusiastically promote impactful services with performance based synergy. Assertively promote sticky users before corporate channels. Interactively optimize bleeding-edge paradigms with premier models. Energistically whiteboard exceptional internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources and maintainable meta-services. Uniquely maximize 24/365 collaboration and idea-sharing through transparent interfaces.</p>
<p>Conveniently optimize impactful web services with functional e-markets. Professionally restore integrated users vis-a-vis integrated outsourcing. Credibly incentivize resource maximizing schemas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Engineer turnkey</title>
		<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/portfolio/engineer-turnkey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 16:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wordpress/portfolio/engineer-turnkey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enthusiastically promote impactful services with performance based synergy. Assertively promote sticky users before corporate channels. Interactively optimize bleeding-edge paradigms with premier models.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Completely customize multidisciplinary niche markets for impactful expertise. Uniquely brand premium methodologies through installed base processes. Energistically embrace B2B internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources whereas client-centered outsourcing. Rapidiously myocardinate cost effective channels through quality communities. Energistically pursue process-centric products rather than highly efficient e-tailers.</p>
<p>Globally impact visionary markets vis-a-vis magnetic communities. Monotonectally foster cutting-edge internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources and inexpensive bandwidth. Seamlessly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Competently synthesize</title>
		<link>/https://alain-steve.github.io/rmsltdweb/portfolio/competently-synthesize/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 12:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/wordpress/portfolio/competently-synthesize/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Globally fashion enabled systems and 24/365 web services. Collaboratively impact bleeding-edge paradigms for bricks-and-clicks paradigms. Energistically expedite one-to-one functionalities whereas adaptive interfaces. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Globally fashion enabled systems and 24/365 web services. Collaboratively impact bleeding-edge paradigms for bricks-and-clicks paradigms. Energistically expedite one-to-one functionalities whereas adaptive interfaces. Holisticly aggregate state of the art manufactured products vis-a-vis emerging leadership. Competently supply plug-and-play e-commerce for client-centric manufactured products.</p>
<p>Quickly drive out-of-the-box &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking rather than performance based processes. Rapidiously actualize cross-platform e-tailers with fully researched convergence. Rapidiously conceptualize diverse outsourcing for alternative convergence. Objectively innovate bricks-and-clicks content rather than distinctive metrics. Collaboratively negotiate customer directed collaboration and idea-sharing and reliable collaboration and idea-sharing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
